Supermarkets have long been suffering as one of the thinnest-margined businesses in existence and one of the least-looked-forward-to places to work or visit.
长期以来，超市一直处境艰难：它是现存各行业中利润最微薄的行业之一，也是人们最不期待去工作或光顾的地方之一。
For more than a decade, they have been under attack from e-commerce giants, blamed for making Americans fat, and accused of contributing to climate change.
十多年来，超市一直受到电商巨头的冲击，被指责让美国人发胖，还被指控加剧了气候变化。
Supermarkets can technically be defined as giants housing 15,000 to 60,000 different products.
严格来说，超市可以定义为容纳15,000到60,000种不同商品的巨型商店。
The revolutionary idea of a self-service grocery, where people could hunt and gather food from aisles rather than asking a clerk to fetch items from behind a counter, first came about in America.
自助式杂货店这一革命性的构想最早出现在美国。在这种店里，人们可以在货架通道间搜寻、采集食物，而不必请店员从柜台后面取出商品。
There is some debate about which was the very first, but over the years a consensus has built around King Kullen Supermarket, founded in New York in 1930.
关于究竟哪一家才是第一家超市，存在一些争议，但多年来，人们逐渐形成了共识，认为是1930年在纽约创立的King Kullen超市。
For some 300 years, Americans had fed themselves from small stores and public markets.
在此之前的大约300年里，美国人一直从小商店和公共市场获取食物来养活自己。
Shopping for food involved mud, noisy chickens, clouds of flies, nasty smells, bargaining, and getting short-changed.
当时，买食物意味着要面对泥泞、吵闹的鸡、成群的苍蝇和难闻的气味，要讨价还价，还会被少找零钱。
The supermarket imitated the Fordist factory, with its emphasis on efficiency and standardization, and reimagined it as a place to buy food.
超市模仿了注重效率和标准化的福特式工厂，并把它重新构想为一个购买食物的场所。
Supermarkets may not feel cutting-edge now, but they were a revolution in distribution at the time.
如今，超市给人的感觉也许算不上前沿，但在当时，它们是一场分销革命。
They were such strange marvels that, on her first official state visit to the United States in 1957, Queen Elizabeth II insisted on an impromptu tour of a suburban-Maryland Giant Food.
超市当时是如此新奇、令人惊叹的事物，以至于伊丽莎白二世女王在1957年首次对美国进行正式国事访问时，坚持要即兴参观马里兰州郊区的一家Giant Food超市。
The typical supermarket layout has barely changed over the past 90 years.
在过去90年里，典型的超市布局几乎没有变化。
Most stores open with flowers, fruit and vegetables at the front as a breath of freshness to arouse our appetite.
大多数门店一进门就摆着鲜花、水果和蔬菜，带来一股清新气息，以激起我们的食欲。
Meanwhile, they keep the milk, eggs, and other daily basics all the way at the back so you’ll travel through as much of the store as possible, and be tempted along the way.
与此同时，门店会把牛奶、鸡蛋和其他日常必需品放在最里头，好让你穿过店内尽可能多的区域，一路上受到诱惑。
In the early days, as the supermarket multiplied, so did our suspicion of it.
早期，随着超市数量成倍增加，我们对它的怀疑也随之倍增。
We have long feared that this “revolution in distribution” uses corporate black magic on our appetite.
长期以来，我们一直担心这场“分销革命”是在对我们的食欲施展企业的黑魔法。
The book The Hidden Persuaders, published in 1957, warned that supermarkets were putting women in a “hypnoidal trance,” causing them to wander aisles bumping into boxes and “picking things off shelves at random.”
1957年出版的《隐藏的说服者》一书警告说，超市正让女性陷入“催眠恍惚状态”，使她们在货架通道间游荡、撞到箱子，并且“随意从货架上拿东西”。